<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>An Avg InfoSec Blog</title>
    <link>https://rootxsudip.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on An Avg InfoSec Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 10:20:22 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://rootxsudip.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying Prototype Pollution for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://rootxsudip.github.io/posts/prototype-pollution-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 10:20:22 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rootxsudip.github.io/posts/prototype-pollution-1/</guid>
      <description>Before diving into prototype pollution we need to learn about javascript objects and prototype basics.&#xA;What is a javascript object? An object in a non-primitive data type which represents a collection of key value pairs. It is to used to store and organize data in a structure manner.&#xA;Example code:&#xA;//Object let car = { name: &amp;#34;audi&amp;#34;, model: &amp;#34;r8&amp;#34;, engine: &amp;#34;V10&amp;#34; } //Accessing object properties console.log(car.name) console.log(car.model) Constructor: Constructor functions are functions used as blueprints for creating multiple instances of objects with similar properties and methods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacking TryHackMe for Fun and Bounties 👀 Part 2</title>
      <link>https://rootxsudip.github.io/posts/hacking-tryhackme-for-fun-and-bounties-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 18:53:44 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rootxsudip.github.io/posts/hacking-tryhackme-for-fun-and-bounties-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Hello guys, here is the 2nd part of blog. This is the most critical bug i have ever found in TryHackMe, using this bug an attacker can edit and delete any rooms of THM.&#xA;I uploaded the POC video to Youtube.&#xA;Shortest Bug Explanation: Any room is edited through a parameter with a room name, i created two room with two different accounts. While deleting/editing the 1st room name i intercepted the request and change the 1st room to 2nd room name, it throwed 403.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacking TryHackMe for Fun and Bounties 👀 Part 1</title>
      <link>https://rootxsudip.github.io/posts/hacking-tryhackme-for-fun-and-bounties-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 09:04:21 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rootxsudip.github.io/posts/hacking-tryhackme-for-fun-and-bounties-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Hello guys, during my hunting i find two vulnerabilities in THM, today i will talk about the first vuln which is S3 Bucket misconfiguration.&#xA;If you don’t know what is s3 bucket and how it leads to vulns check the references.&#xA;1. S3 Bucket Misconfiguation Leads to deletion of any images(profile,room images,banner etc..) When, uploading my profile pic, i saw it was uploaded to a s3 bucket.&#xA;My first thought was can i perform read, upload and delete operation in the S3 bucket?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Was I Able to Delete Any Account of an Organization Using Idor</title>
      <link>https://rootxsudip.github.io/posts/how-was-i-able-to-delete-any-account-of-an-organization-using-idor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 09:37:47 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rootxsudip.github.io/posts/how-was-i-able-to-delete-any-account-of-an-organization-using-idor/</guid>
      <description>Hello, amazing hackers my name is Sudip Roy and i am an InfoSec student and part-time Bug Hunter.This is my first writeup about a critical vulnerability which i found on a website(Vdp). Hope you guys will like it and learn something new from it.&#xA;Lets get started, The website provides cloud-based consumer identity and access management (CIAM) solution. For testing purposes i signup using my account, select developer pro(extra features), created a app and looked for every features of the website, 1 hour later i decided to play with the delete account feature from the settings page.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
